Hi everyone, welcome, it's Celine and this is a new video on my channel. I received seven new pieces from LeoHacks.
A lot of spandex, a PU, a swimwear bodysuit, a swimsuit basically.
And I have a lot to do now, so I will just start right away with the first outfit.
First piece and I decided to show you something black first, the colorful stuff will come later.
but yeah this is a what do you call it I mean it's not a catsuit because it has no arms
it's not a swimsuit because it has long legs so what kind of garment is this is it a sports suit
or help me out here what would you say what would you call it anyway what I can tell you about it is
that it's really comfortable and really smooth and I'm wearing size large but don't be confused
I'll tell you more about the Asian sizing and the Leo Hex sizing a bit later in the video.
If you know my channel already a bit longer then you may have noticed that this is my second Leo
Hex video already and the first one was the video on my channel that reached 1 million views
which was quite a success or still is quite a success and it was also a video that may have
taken a part in the demonetization of my channel but I still like it and if you want to support
this channel then hit the subscribe button or check out my patreon anyway I'm going to show
you more of the cool Leo Hex outfits. I have to turn around to have a look in the back again
myself. I really like the style of back cutouts, racing backs, whatever. And Leo Hex launched a
new collection, which is part of this video and which I'm going to show you now. Okay, so I would
say this is blue blue color yeah blue gray ish whatever um this is the new collection of leo
hex and it's called dive suit i think but of course it's not actually for diving but the
stitching and the look reminds a bit of wetsuits overall and i talked to the owner of leo hex he
that yeah you can probably go snorkeling or windsurfing with it no problem so you
can wear it at the beach or in the water for example it shouldn't be problem
I'm going to turn around for you guys and I can also tell you that it is size
extra large XL it fits really good and maybe you noticed that it is a different
size than the one before but tip I can give you check the size chart because
the size chart is correct and it is quite a bit different for every article so do not just order
one size for everything but read people read okay the zipper here I can close it which is okay I
like it open a bit more but I can also do something else and there's a second zipper which I can open
and I have like kind of a keyhole cleo cheer and of course now you can see my bra I would have to
wear without the bra for the perfect look so to say but I think you can imagine that
and maybe this is my favorite option because it's something different and not your usual average
cut you get with bodysuits so I think it's quite handy to have these three options available
oh where is it here same bodysuit different color obviously black and this is also a size smaller
so this is size large and I think you can tell it's a bit more snug I can also say that it's
shorter in the length so I realized that there's more touching going on also in
the back but yeah I managed to squeeze into it I mean the material is pretty
stretchy so that's what's helping of course but I would still prefer size X
rush because it's a bit more comfortable and of course you also have the three
ways to appear. The new collection has overall four different colors. I already
showed you two of them but I have the other two colors here with slightly
different cut in the bodysuits and also again a different size. Extra extra large
and I don't know if it'll fit or if it's going to be too big. We'll find out
together. So as expected Xtra Xtra Large is a bit too big but the color is nice.
It's a metallic purple and the design is sleeveless and the zipper is in the back
this time which is quite the opposite to the other ones. Yeah but I have another one
I'm going to show you next. Alright this of course fits better it's again size
extra large and sleeveless the zipper is in the front again so like the black and
gray one basically also I can close it and then you see there is like a kind of
a turtleneck color here so a bit higher and I can also open this again I still
like this feature and close it. And we have a Leo Hex signature here in the leg cut out.
You can also turn around and of course it's my personal choice but I like the two long arm
bodysuits in this material and from the new collection better than this one. Although this
one is also nice but I still like the metallic blue color most but it looks nice together with
the tights at least oh by the way if you're wondering about the tights um they're from
woolford they're called neon 40 and the shine is just out of this world kind of I know but I will
abandoned than now because I have a full bodysuit next. A bit of a similar color to this one
and really
like basic catsuit pattern so I'm going to change a catsuit and I think this is
It's the lightest color in a while I've worn.
It's not completely white.
It's like a silverish.
And compared to the shoes of course you can see that it's not white.
I'm wearing a size large.
And the overall fit is okay.
But it's a bit too short for me.
So I guess it would fit a person better that's like a few centimeters shorter or smaller.
I'm really happy that the bodysuits from before fits the good regarding the length because I
noticed quite often that Asian sizing is a bit problematic for really tall people like me also with the
length of the arms and stuff.
I'm 1 meter 73 tall and the size large would fit perfectly for like an
EU 43 46 size, not as tall as I am.
But again the material is really stretchy and it's also really smooth so very
silky and it feels nice and I think the reflections are also nice with the
lights and you can basically tell from the look of it that it's really slippery
material. Really smooth. For the last item it's a swimsuit and it is my personal wish so I'm really
happy to show you the next one. It's a really cool swimsuit with black and gold and this looks like
kind of ink splatter pattern here and I saw it and I was like oh I want to try this one. This one
looks so cool I'm not the biggest fan of one piece swimwear but this is just an eye catcher
I think also the back is really open it's more than your normal racer back swimwear style
so you have to see it from both sides for the overall impression and I think it's a really
cool one totally gonna wear this one for my next swimwear video or for my next um yeah trip to the
pool or to the lake because it's also really comfy there was a lot to see today a lot of outfits a
lot of colors and i hope you enjoyed it please leave a thumbs up if you like the video and
write a comment down below and tell me about your favorite piece because uh what was my favorite
piece actually I don't know I think this one of course and maybe the long arms bodysuit the
blue one metallic blue one yeah probably that one too and maybe also the black one because it's
black I don't know never mind um I hope you had a good time and I'll see you in the next video
check out everything in the description text because I'll link of course the shop
and all the products see ya bye
Thank you.